<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OPS Consulting Mobile</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="our_companytitle">About Our Company</string>

    <string name="analyticstitle">Intelligence Analytics and Training</string>

    <string name="careerstitle">Careers</string>

    <string name="contact_ustitle">Contact Us</string>

    <string name="marketstitle">Markets We Serve</string>

    <string name="newseventstitle">News and Events</string>

    <string name="qactititle">Defensible Estimating for Software</string>

    <string name="setatitle">SETA &amp; Acquisition Support</string>

    <string name="softwaretitle">Software and Systems Development</string>

    <string name="analyticsmain">OPS Consulting partners some of the largest analytic contracts
        in the IC because of our comprehensive understanding of the entire analytic life-cycle.
        Our analysts have created unique, in-depth training which leads junior analysts through
        three levels of training in analytic tradecraft. Analysts then move to mission work
        centers and contribute immediately to clients\' missions. Seasoned analysts have worked
        side-by-side with software engineers developing new tools for tomorrow\'s analysts. OPS
        analysts specialize in:
        \n\u2022    Collection\n
        \n\u2022    Signals analysis\n
        \n\u2022    Cyber Analysis\n
        \n\u2022    Linguistics\n
        \n\u2022    Imagery Analysis\n
        \n\u2022    HUMINT\n
        \n\u2022    All-source Intelligence analysis</string>

    <string name ="growingtheanalystmain">Today, we see more and more attacks to our personal and
        corporate digital fingerprints, yet little is being done to prevent further intrusions.
        However, the OPS Consulting ‘Growing the Analyst’ curriculum, developed by Department of
        Defense contract analysts, is a foundational template for participants to build the
        knowledge, skills and abilities that are required to become a Cyber Analyst in today’s fast
        paced net environments. This curriculum focuses on both technical proficiency and
        non-technical core competencies that create practitioners who are job ready as soon as they
        finish training.</string>

    <string name="AACC">    AACC is a public, two year, open-admission institution that offers credit
        and non-credit courses. AACC is designated as a Center of Academic Excellence in Information
        Assurance Two Year Education (CAE2Y) by the NSA and the U.S. Department of Homeland Security.
        AACC is also the first academic institution to be designated by the Defense Cyber Crime
        Center (DC3) as a National Center of Digital Forensics Academic Excellence (CDFAE). AACC’s
        CyberCenter brings the resources of the college directly to business and government
        organizations with Cybersecurity training needs. The CyberCenter is dedicated to meeting the
        workforce needs of government organizations and industry by developing professionals who are
        Cybersecurity aware, have the ability to operate, maintain, protect and defend information
        technology systems and networks, as well as investigate and analyze cyber events and crimes
        after they occur. </string>

    <string name="Afcea">AFCEA Central Maryland Chapter (AFCEA-CMD) is a non-profit membership
        association dedicated to providing an ethical, interactive forum for sharing knowledge and
        building relationships across government, military, industry and academia.
        \nOur Chapter focuses primarily on enabling the intelligence missions of today and tomorrow
        through education and investment in talented people. We accomplish our goal by promoting the
        continuing education of current IT professionals, and supporting the education of future
        leaders in Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics (STEM). Each year, proceeds from
        our corporate sponsors and Chapter events enable us to award over $200,000 to qualified
        students and teachers through direct scholarship, endowment or grant.
        \nThe fastest growing and third largest chapter within AFCEA International, AFCEA-CMD includes
        over 1800 professionals working in and around the Fort George G. Meade area. </string>

    <string name="networkattackstr">OPS Consulting is quickly becoming a leader in offensive
        computer network operations capabilities. OPS Consulting\'s outstanding team of analysts
        can quickly develop target templates for cyber target development, provide operational
        planning teams with all source analysis products to meet DoD and combatant commander\'s
        requirements.
        \n OPS Consulting\'s analysts will also work with your cyber planners to identify critical
        intelligence gaps which will lead to the development of new intelligence reports.</string>

    <string name="networkdefensestr">Defense team analysts perform defensive cyberspace operations
        to support Department of Defense mission objectives. Analysts perform network analysis and
        reporting of current threats to critical national infrastructure and information systems.
        \n Some defense team network analysts have formal training and military experience in
        securing DoD networks. Specifically, we have knowledge of:
        \n
        \n\u2022    Experience with DoD 5200 series\n
        \n\u2022    Experience with DoD 8580.1\n
        \n\u2022    Experience with DIACAP\n
        \n\u2022    Experience with NIAP\n
        \n\u2022    Experience with CJCSI_6510</string>

    <string name="networkexplostr">OPS Consulting\'s senior network intelligence analysts works
        efficiently and diligently to develop new network accesses. Network intelligence analysts
        understand complex network infrastructure, information systems, network protocols, and
        network topology to create an environment for offensive cyberspace operations.</string>

    <string name="networkoperationsstr">The growing number of attacks on our cyber networks has
        become, in President Obama\'s words, "one of the most serious economic and national security threats our nation faces."
        \n OPS Consulting is leading the way in Computer Network Operations by building one of the
        best teams in cyber operations. OPS Consulting\'s cyber team provides superior intelligence
        support to protect federal government networks and, ultimately, critical infrastructure on
        which we all depend. OPS Consulting works across the federal government and partners with
        the private sector to promote cyber security knowledge and innovation.</string>

    <string name="companyabout">OPS Consulting uses the power of technology and the science of
        engineering to help guide its clients toward high-value and high-performance, customized
        systems engineering, software development, and business management solutions. To help you
        achieve mission objectives, we join your team to learn everything we can, develop and help
        to build a comprehensive plan to achieve your goals.
        \n
        \n Since our founding in 1999, we have focused on building a strong corporate culture that
        advocates teamwork and professionalism, integrity in all we do, and a focus on delivering
        exceptional customer-focused results.
        \n
        \n <b>We consistently deliver successful projects by:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022    Developing IT applications quickly and cost-effectively, implementing solutions that meet
        the customer needs.\n
        \n\u2022    Applying innovative technologies that improve productivity and process
        efficiencies, while lowering capital expenses.\n
        \n\u2022    Reducing IT complexities to minimize risks.\n
        \n\u2022    Adapting to client needs.\n
        \n\u2022    Responding to market changes and technological advancements.\n
        \n\u2022    Working collaboratively to minimize disruptions to mission continuity, whatever that mission
        happens to be.
        \n
        \n <b>What makes us different:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022    100% dedication to customer needs\n
        \n\u2022    Disciplined and systematic, yet agile, approaches deliver successful results consistently,
        rapidly, and cost effectively.\n
        \n\u2022    Company culture that focuses on hiring the best, empowering employees, encouraging open
        communication, inspiring leadership, encouraging professional development, and acting with
        integrity in all we do.</string>

    <string name="companyachievements1"><b>Computer Network Attack, Computer Network Defense and Forensic Analysis</b>
        \n On numerous contracts, OPS cyber security personnel developed and implemented sophisticated solutions,
        including software, techniques, tool, and methodologies, that protect, secure, and exploit information.
\n
        \n <b>Engineering and Constructing Secure IT systems</b>
        \nOur system architects and engineers apply industry standards and ingenuity to create secure systems.
        We take advantage of the latest technologies (SOA, cloud computing, etc.) that scale to encompass huge
        volumes of data for ingest, processing, storage, and dissemination. Our software developers create
        secure applications to enable access, manipulation, mining, analysis, storage, and output of this data.
        \n
        \n <b>Signals Intelligence and Information Operations</b>
        \nOn a number of contracts, OPS personnel use skillsets in signals measurement and analysis, digital
        signals analysis and processing, signals collection, research and analysis, data mining, reporting,
        processing, geospatial metadata analysis, all-source intelligence analysis, PROFORMA and Multi-INT sources.</string>


    <string name="companyachievements2"><b>IT System Administration and Analysis</b>
        \nOur personnel are responsible for building and maintaining high-performance IT solutions that keep
        mission-critical systems up and running 24x7, 365 days a year.
\n
        \nBased on a thorough analysis of current infrastructure, we build cost-effective, long-term support
        solutions for managing networks and systems. For our development customers, we build and manage
        laboratories capable of simultaneously running multiple operating systems and simulating different
        testing platforms.
\n
        \n <b>Acquisition Support and Program Management</b>
        \nOPS supports large ACAT-1 programs throughout their lifecycle, providing system engineering,
        acquisition support, cost analysis and estimating, and financial and program management services.
\n
        \nUsing a set of repeatable processes and tools that we have developed and finely tuned, OPS Consulting’s
        key technical staff translate program requirements into cost drivers that are traceable from concept
        through development, production, operation, and support. We provide training and customized EVMS
        implementations to monitor programs and help organizations achieve success. </string>

    <string name="companyachievements3"> Our proprietary Quality Assessment Capability has been used to
        analyze more than 750,000,000 lines of code. Once we understand code that is currently in place
        in an application, we provide clients with appropriate cost estimates for software projects.</string>

    <string name="companycommunity1">OPS Consulting is proud to announce our 3rd annual Charity Golf Outing!
        This year\'s charitable donations will help support the Special Operations Warrior Foundation. This
        organization provides college scholarships and counseling services for the children of our fallen
        veterans as well as financial assistance to severely wounded special operations personnel. </string>

    <string name="companycommunity2">CAMP HOPE Inc. is a non-profit organization consisting of volunteers who
        gather every summer in Frostburg, Maryland to help needy families and individuals from Allegany County
        and the surrounding areas to upgrade their homes.
        \nEach summer, over 400 youth and adults explore and share their Christian faith and fellowship and repair
        between 55 and 60 homes during a four-week period. The individuals and families served receive home
        rehabilitation, home winterization, and safer homes, as well as a new hope for the future. </string>

    <string name="companycommunity3">The mission of the PKD foundation is to promote programs of research,
        advocacy, education, support and awareness in order to discover treatments and a cure for
        Polycystic Kidney Disease and improve the lives of all it affects.
        \nThe PKD Foundation has come a long way since its first year of funding research - one grant for
        only $25,000. In 2009, the PKD Foundation funded 32 projects in five countries for a total of
        nearly $2 million. With the support of so many, the PKD Foundation has built an expansive and
        passionate volunteer network of national events, such as the Walk for PKD and Run for PKD. </string>

    <string name="companyleadership">Our phenomenal team of smart, dedicated employees work to build
        strong relationships with clients, which has directly contributed to the steady growth of OPS Consulting.
        \n
        \n <b>Leadership</b>
        \nOPS Consulting\'s executive team has a depth and breadth of engineering and business management expertise
        that is among the best in the field. They work closely with our employees and partners to chart the continual
        success and growth of the company.
        \n
        \nOur Board of Advisors are respected leaders in the technology and government communities who bring vision and
        a deep network of contacts to OPS Consulting. Their invaluable advice and support guides the implementation
        of our core competencies and strategies.
        \n
        \nKey personnel are hand-selected for their reputation as team players who apply high standards and provide
        superlative customer service to elevate the company above the competition.
        \n
        \nEach member of our team collaborates closely with our customers to fully understand their needs and build
        customized products and services around those needs.</string>

    <string name="greg"><b>Greg Foley
        \nFounder and Chief Executive Officer</b>
        \n
        \nGreg is an industry innovator who has earned global recognition for his development and management of
        software systems.
        \nPrior to establishing OPS Consulting, he was a co-owner of Coastal Research Technology, and he worked for
        10 years at Lockheed Martin Missiles and Space.
        \nHe received his B.S. from the University of Maryland, Baltimore County, and a Masters of Computer Science
        from Johns Hopkins University.
        \nGreg lives in Crownsville, Maryland with his wife and three children.</string>

    <string name="steve"><b>Stephen Cummins
        \nDirector</b>
        \n
        \nStephen is responsible for operations and strategic planning, with a specific focus on developing new
        strategies and opportunities to enhance client services.
        \nPrior to joining OPS, Stephen was Director of Accounting Policy at Citigroup. During his tenure, he
        integrated multiple business acquisitions, including Travelers Group\'s acquisition of Citibank (forming
        Citigroup in 1998) and Citigroup\'s acquisition of The Associates in 2000. He was also responsible for
        the financial oversight of Citicorp Trust Bank, whose assets grew from $800 million to $32 billion over
        a seven-year timeframe, and he led a number of large-scale projects, including the implementation of a
        program to conform to the requirements of Sarbanes Oxley for the 2004 reporting period.
        \nPrior to Citigroup, Stephen held positions at Alexander and Alexander Services, an international insurance
        brokerage, and with Coca Cola Enterprises and KPMG Peat Marwick.
        \nHe is a Certified Public Accountant and holds a B.A. in Business Administration from Seattle University.</string>

    <string name="jim"> <b> Jim Galvin
        \nChief Operating Officer </b>
        \n
        \nJim manages day-to-day operations for OPS Consulting, leading our client-facing staff, building relationships
        with our business partners, and engaging with clients in each market that OPS supports. He also serves as
        Program Manager for some OPS contracts.
        \nAfter 20-plus years as a government employee within the Intelligence Community, concluding as a Deputy
        Program Executive Officer (PEO), Jim moved to the private sector, spending the last several years as a
        Program Manager and as a consultant to multiple agencies within both the IC and the Department of Defense.
        He holds a Bachelor’s Degree from the University of Maryland at College Park, a Master’s Degree from The
        Johns Hopkins University, and a Master’s Degree from the National Defense University’s Industrial College
        of the Armed Forces, or ICAF (now The Dwight D. Eisenhower School for National Security and Resource Strategy).
        \nJim resides in Eldersburg, Maryland, with his wife, a teacher in the Carroll County Public School System,
        one daughter, one son, and one cantankerous English Bulldog, Mainzer, who is named for her original hometown.</string>

    <string name="bill"><b>Bill Douglas
        \nChief Strategy Officer</b>
        \n
        \nBill is responsible for assisting the Executive team with developing, executing and sustaining the strategic
        initiatives of the company. Bill will lead the business development initiatives and insure they support the
        strategic corporate plan for OPS.
        \nWith more than 35 years working in the Information Technology industry, Bill has provided business
        development, project management, and engineering expertise within the Federal government sector. Prior to
        joining OPS, Bill was the Chief Executive Officer for COMSO Inc., delivering leadership in business development,
        project management, sales, management oversite and corporate financial planning. Bill has held several Director,
        Manager and Engineering roles with other IT companies such has Northrop Grumman, Newbridge Networks, Silicon
        Graphics and Digital Equipment Corporation. Bill has a Project Management Professional (PMP) certification from
        the Project Management Institute and is an IT Infrastructure Library (ITIL) v3 certified professional. He holds
        a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Information Systems from California State University.
        \nBill resides in Severna Park with his wife and is fortunate to have all three children living within the local
        area to enjoy together the boating, sailing and outdoor sports of Maryland.</string>

    <string name="ben"> <b> Ben Safford
        \nDirector, Intelligence Analytics &amp; Training Division </b>
\n
        \nBen manages Ops Consulting’s Analyst Division, which provides Intelligence, Language, and Technical
        Analysis services to clients within the Intelligence Community.
        \nBen started his career with the Air Force as an Intelligence Analyst. After his six-year enlistment,
        he worked as a Network Analyst for Booz Allen Hamilton. In late 2012, Ben moved to Ops Consulting as
        a Cyber Analyst Support Specialist. He has a Bachelor’s degree in Information Systems and holds multiple
        IT certifications.
        \nBen joined the Air Force from the Chicago area but now lives in Brooklyn Park with his wife, Denise,
        and his four children. He enjoys spending time with his family and coaching youth sports. During his
        spare time, Ben enjoys watching his favorite sports teams, to include the Chicago Cubs.</string>

    <string name="mark"><b>Mark Houston-Ludlam
        \nDirector of Software and Systems Development Division</b>
\n
        \nMark manages the Software and Systems Development team which provides services in the areas of analytic
        tools, big data analytics, system administration and others for the DoD community and other customers.
        \nMark joined OPS Consulting in 2014 when OPS acquired Frontier Technologies, Inc. Mark was Vice President
        and Co-owner of Frontier Technologies for over 26 years. Previous experience includes the design and
        development of a variety of systems ranging from embedded tactical aircraft systems to enterprise level
        data management and visualization systems. Mark has unique experience in the areas of system performance
        evaluation and optimization.
        \nMark has a Bachelor\'s Degree from the University of California in Physics. He is currently pursuing
        certification as a Splunk System Architect. Mark lives in Lothian, Maryland with his wife, son and daughter
        where they raise pastured livestock. He has one other daughter who is pursuing a medical degree at Washington
        University in Saint Louis.</string>

    <string name="brenda"><b>Brenda Cope
        \nDirector of Systems Engineering &amp; Technical Assistance (SETA) Services Division</b>
\n
        \nBrenda has over 25+ years of diversified experience in Contracts Management, Project Management,
        Acquisition Management, and Financial/Resource Management both as a civilian and contractor supporting
        various federal government agencies. She holds a Bachelor’s Degree from the University of Maryland in
        Business &amp; Management as well as two industry-recognized certifications, Defense Acquisition Workforce
        Improvement Act (DAWIA) certification in Business Management and a Program Management Professional (PMP)
        certification from the Program Management Institute (PMI).
        \nAt OPS Consulting Brenda is responsible for the SETA team who provide consulting services across
        multiple functional areas within the DoD and IC. Prior to joining OPS Consulting, Brenda held the following
        corporate roles of Program Manager, Contracts Manager and Senior Business Manager at a number of small
        businesses. She thrives in networking, forming alliances, and participating in cross-functional teams who
        are working towards a common goal, whether in business or personal life.
        \nBrenda resides in Ellicott City, Maryland, with her husband and “kitty” named Chester. She enjoys spending
        time with their children and grandchildren in nearby communities as well as traveling, boating, and musical
        entertainment. The last concert they attended was in NYC at Madison Square Gardens to see Fleetwood Mac.</string>

    <string name="companystrategic1"><b>Over the years, we have developed a reputation for excellence with our prime contractors by:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Actively participating in proposal work\n
        \n\u2022 Providing fully qualified candidates\n
        \n\u2022 Training our staff to help them excel\n
        \n\u2022 Hiring staff that are high achievers\n
        \n\u2022 Retaining staff through management attention, fun, rewards, and work/life balance\n
        \n\u2022 Responsive and outstanding service to our mutual customers
        \n
        \n<b>Companies we do business with:</b>
        \n </string>

    <string name="companystrategic2"> As a prime contractor for the U.S. Department of Defense as well as other
         government and corporate clients, OPS Consulting is positioned to enhance subcontractor opportunities and
        competitiveness.
        \n
        \n<b>We pledge to:</b>
\n
        \n\u2022 Provide opportunities to teammates to join with OPS in mission-focused service to the government\n
        \n\u2022 Foster a wholesome team environment\n
        \n\u2022 Be fair in distributing the work amongst teammates\n
        \n\u2022 Communicate with teammates regularly- progress, issues, awards\n
        \n\u2022 Allow teammates to develop, staff and manage tasks under our contracts</string>

    <string name="qacbody">The Quality Assessment Capability (QAC) is a powerful, effective, state-of-the-art process to quantify the quality of software
        applications for the purpose of engineering highly reliable and maintainable products. The quality assessment is conducted in a static environment
        and compares the software measures of the application against other domain specific applications and/or industry standards.
        \nOur signature product has analyzed over 750,000,000 lines of code to provide defensible estimating for software projects. The QAC is a highly
        extensible and flexible methodology which is rapidly adaptable to a variety of customer needs, emerging technologies, and diverse measurement objectives.
        \n
        \n<b>QAC provides "actionable information" to decision-makers, beyond what standard metric tools offer. This objective, substantive information
        assists in:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Contractor evaluation\n
        \n\u2022 Processing corrections to ongoing development efforts\n
        \n\u2022 Measuring the quality of software code for comparisons with other applications\n
        \n\u2022 Setting a threshold rating for the quality of future application code deliverables\n
        \n\u2022 Guiding future migration decisions\n
        \n\u2022 Identifying sources of risk\n
        \n\u2022 Providing a review of the software lifecycle risks associated with multi-component systems\n
        \n\u2022 Comparing systems-independent of language, platform, architecture, etc.\n
        \n\u2022 Guiding software build, buy, or re-use decisions
        \n
        \n<b>QAC supports:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Configuration management\n
        \n\u2022 Quality assurance\n
        \n\u2022 Testing\n
        \n\u2022 Independent verification and validation\n
        \n\u2022 Metrics programs\n
        \n\u2022 Cost estimation\n
        \n\u2022 Quality and reliability engineering\n
        \n\u2022 Risk management\n
        \n\u2022 Project management\n
        \n\u2022 Statistical process control\n
        \n\u2022 Product certification\n
        \n\u2022 Cost and benefit analysis\n
        \n\u2022 Return on investment analysis\n
        \n\u2022 Process improvement\n
        \n\u2022 Capability Maturity Model assessments\n
        \n\u2022 Business process reengineering\n
        \n\u2022 ISO 9001 registration\n
    </string>

    <string name="softqualanastr">OPS Consulting\'s focus on customer success during software development
        has led to the development the Quality Assessment Capability, a proprietary product that quantifies
        the quality of software applications and allows us to engineer highly reliable and maintainable
        products. The assessment is conducted in a static environment and compares the software measures
        and metrics of the application against other domain specific applications and industry standards.
        There are several benefits to the acquisition professional using this suite of tools that assess
        software size, maintainability, complexity, and security features that directly drive a development
        program\'s acquisition and support costs.
        \n
        \n<b>Reuse:</b>
        \nQAC\'s suite of tools has the ability to independently identify, analyze, and evaluate a code\'s
        ability to be reused. Through these proprietary QAC developed tools – such as J-JOC, X-Ray, and Socket
        – QAC can quickly determine the code\'s quality, maintainability, and security posture for the cost
        estimator to determine the cost effectiveness of reusing this heritage software. This eliminates the
        ambiguity and potential pitfalls of incorporating reuse as a cost savings measure in software estimates.
        By effectively analyzing reuse or heritage code, the acquisition professional can now affect cost risk
        through proper code analysis.
        \n
        \n<b>Measure:</b>
        \nQAC has developed innovative tools and techniques that have automated software measurement for speed
        and accuracy. Through its CodeMetrics™ tool, which is also available in a GOTS form, QAC can quickly
        and easily count potentially any language type currently being used in the market today with the ease
        of a mouse click. Additionally, QAC employs the standard function point counting techniques of IFPUG,
        thus providing even more accuracy when measuring structured language development. Where QAC takes
        software estimation to the next generation is in the engagement of Object Oriented (OO) estimating.
        When software development programs use a more modern OO design method, which is becoming very common,
        traditional SLOC or Function Point counting can dangerously skew the size of the development effort.
        By matching an OO estimating method to its native OO development environment, QAC eliminated the common
        translation error and produces more accurate, more defendable, and more traceable cost estimates, thus
        keeping the acquisition professional on the cutting edge of software cost estimating techniques.
        \n
        \n<b>Estimating:</b>
        \nQAC works with existing estimating tools that have established track records in the estimating
        community, but where QAC goes beyond these parametric tools is in how it integrates them into one
        user format. QAC has developed a tool called AutoRisk™, which is also available in a GOTS form,
        that has greatly increased software estimating productivity through its simple user interface and
        convenient exportable outputs. Additionally, QAC has been integrated with one of the leading commercial
        tools for OO estimating. The incorporation of such tools into QAC allows the acquisition professional
        to stay current with modern development practices.
        \n
        \n<b>QAC Implementation</b>
        \nQAC is meant to be a lean application of software analysis, and the implementation of QAC capabilities
        is driven by the scope and expediency of the requirements. QAC can be implemented through the deployment
        of QAC analysts as an imbedded yet pooled group of resources at the disposal of estimating leadership.
        Depending on the scope and requirements, QAC analysts support the estimating team with developing the
        software specific portions of the estimate, and this allows for software- focused expertise working on
        this critical area of the larger system. By also pooling the QAC resources, QAC analysts track and manage
        software estimates across the enterprise synthesizing the resultant data and providing ever improving
        software metrics, development stating, and software final product analysis.
        \n
        \n<b>QAC Impact</b>
        \nQAC capabilities have been employed on several programs with the DoD and Intelligence community, and our
        tools have been used to analyze over 200 million lines of code on hundreds of software programs.
        \n
        \nIn summary, QAC provides the most extensive and technologically advanced software estimating capability
        available on the market. The developed and commercial tools we bring, along with our growing staff of
        qualified software professionals, provide cost estimating agencies with the power and insight needed to
        accurately estimate the most complex acquisition programs today.</string>

    <string name="softdevqac">Custom software development is built using OPS\' Quality Assessment Capability,
        a proprietary product that quantifies the quality of software applications and allows us to ensure all
        software is operationally efficient, secure, and up to our high standards.

        \n OPS software development experts work closely with customers to understand the complexities of their
        design requirements. We use industry software development standards for efficiency and seamless
        integration with existing legacy software and systems.</string>

    <string name="setamain">At OPS Consulting, we understand that success requires more than innovative technical solutions.
        Requirements gathering, planning, acquisition expertise, budget oversight, and risk management, combined with
        deep understanding of the customer domain, are each crucial pieces to a successful program.
\n
        \n Engineering Management isn\'t "one size fits all." Processes and strategies must be tailored to the needs
        of each individual project. Our expertise spans the entire program life-cycle - all of the knowledge and
        experience needed to support every phase of a technology program.
        \n
        <b>\nOur SETA specialties include:</b>
\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Program management\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Risk Assessment and Management\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Contracting &amp; Business Management\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Requirements Analysis and Management\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Configuration Management\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Independent Validation &amp; Verification\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Process Engineering\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Quality Assurance\n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Earned Value Management</string>

    <string name="setamissionsupport">
        Provide knowledgeable and experienced mission specialists to support our customers in achieving operational
        mission objectives through decision making at the executive, management, and operational mission levels.
        These individual are subject matter experts in specific fields of study. </string>

    <string name="setacquisitionsupport">Our experienced professionals help the government manage all stages of the
        DoD 5000 Milestone Decision Process for Major Automated Information Systems at the ACAT-1 level and below
        for the Intelligence Community. We lead the generation of support documentation including Acquisition Strategies,
        Capabilities Development Document/Capabilities Production Document, Clinger Cohen compliance documents and the
        full complement of solicitation documents and plans once the government is ready to proceed with procurement.</string>

    <string name="setacostandscanalysis">When accurate, defensible life cycle cost estimation is required, OPS
        Consulting brings a unique strategy to bear that our clients depend on. Our repeatable and customizable
        process is characterized by having our analysts working with clients to understand technical, programmatic,
        and cost baselines at all stages within a program life cycle.
\n
        \nOPS Consulting\'s key technical staff translate program requirements into cost drivers that are traceable
        from concept, development, production, operation, and support. Our process in which we closely coordinate
        with technical and program management staff enables our experienced subject matter experts to provide defensible
        analyses. OPS Consulting can facilitate your full decision support of acquisition, procurement, and
        operational implementations.</string>

    <string name="setaprogrammanagement">OPS professionals are skilled in agile program management methods and
        can tailor our approach to each individual program. We provide a focus on efficiently and effectively
        meeting our customers\' mission and business objectives. Our program managers are DAWIA or PMI certified
        PMP professionals that manage every aspect of program development including cost, schedule, functional,
        and quality assurance performance.</string>

    <string name="softwareandsystemsdevstr">Highly-qualified and experienced professionals at OPS perform
        software engineering and systems integration. We take an agile approach to software development
        and systems integration. Our experts are attentive to customer requirements and create purpose-built
        solutions. We fund ongoing training for our employees in cutting-edge technologies that complement
        our clients\' missions.
        \n
        \n<b>Our engineering and integration experience includes:</b>
        \n
        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Quantum &amp; HPC Computing\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Machine Learning\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Big Data\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Real-Time Streaming Analytics\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Prototyping\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Splunk Enterprise Applications\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 System &amp; Software Architecture\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 System Development &amp; Integration\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Automated Software Testing\n

        \n\u0009\u0009\u2022 Software Quality Assurance\n
        \n
        \n Customers benefit from our competencies due to the way our software engineering and systems integration
        practices revolve around Agile processes such as Scrum. Scrum is a fluid and flexible way of development
        and focuses on being adaptable and implementing solutions throughout the lifecycle process. Customers come
        first, and by remaining agile, we are able to give them a clear view of a project from start to finish. </string>

    <string name="softwaredatabasestr">OPS Consulting provides database development services for Cloud
        Implementations, MSSQL, MySQL, Oracle, Sybase, and Access databases. We use the latest development
        technologies to ensure that your custom application will function properly. Our experienced database
        developers can work directly with your in-house staff or, if the situation dictates, develop the entire
        project from design through training and implementation.
        \n
        \n<b>Our Database Engineering specialties include design, development, and administration of:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 RDBMS : Oracle 8i Ð 11g, Sybase databases, MySQL databases, MS Access DB databases\n
        \n\u2022 CLOUD : HADOOP, Hive, Pig, ZooKeeper </string>

    <string name="systemsadminstr">Building and maintaining high-performance IT solutions is our goal
        when meeting the IT needs of our customers. From a thorough analysis of the current infrastructure
        to setting up a cost-effective, long-term support solution, the OPS Consulting team helps customers
        meet their objectives.
        \n
        \n<b>Our system administration expertise includes:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Linux, Solaris and Windows operating systems\n

        \n\u2022 Enterprise server administration\n

        \n\u2022 Desktop platforms, thick and thin client\n

        \n\u2022 Network routers, bridges and gateway administration\n

        \n\u2022 SAN, DAS, and NAS storage solutions\n

        \n\u2022 Disaster recovery\n

        \n\u2022 Virtualization technologies\n

        \n\u2022 High performance computing</string>
    
    <string name="softwareengineeringstr">At OPS Consulting, we bring together a core set of software
        development capabilities, perfected with best practices gained over years of experience. Coupled
        with domain knowledge, we apply these software development capabilities to a focused set of
        solutions and services to help our customer\'s meet their mission critical objectives.
        \n
        \n <b>Our Software Engineering specialties include:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Custom software applications design and development using:\n

        \n\u2022 Object Oriented Development : Java, J2EE, JSP, Servlets, C++\n

        \n\u2022 Microsoft : Visual Basic, VB.Net, VBA\n

        \n\u2022 Scripting : Perl, JavaScript, VB Script, PHP\n

        \n\u2022 Mark Up-Languages : HTML, DHTML, XML, XSL, XHTML\n

        \n\u2022 Cloud Technologies : Hbase, Pig, Hive, ZooKeeper, Mahout</string>

    <string name="systemengineeringstr">OPS Consulting\'s system engineers have experience in all aspects
        of the system development lifecycle. We provide requirements analysis and management, Interface
        Control Document (ICD) development, Concept of Operations (CONOP) development, and enterprise
        and system architecture development. We utilize an interdisciplinary engineering management process
        encompassing the desired set of system solutions to satisfy customer needs. The big-picture is
        always maintained through effective communication with our customer and an in depth knowledge of
        the integrated life-cycle behind every system.
        \n
        \n<b>Our System Engineering specialties include:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Enterprise Architecture (SYSTEM ARCHITECT and C4ISR)\n

        \n\u2022 Process Re-Engineering\n

        \n\u2022 Business Analysis\n

        \n\u2022 Systems Analysis\n

        \n\u2022 System Design\n

        \n\u2022 Systems Integration</string>
    
    <string name="networkengineeringstr">With 10 years of experience in the engineering, design, testing, operation, administration, maintenance, and troubleshooting of wide-area and local area networks in both commercial and Government environments, the OPS Consulting Network Engineering team is widely recognized as key contributors to major network systems.
        \n
        \n<b>Our Network Engineering specialties include:</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Network Design, Administration, Security, and Engineering\n

        \n\u2022 WAN, LAN, and SAN technologies\n

        \n\u2022 ATM, GigaBit Ethernet\n

        \n\u2022 Network and Application Security\n

        \n\2022 Network Traffic Monitoring and Timing\n

        \n\u2022 Program Management Support\n

        \n\u2022 O/S expertise (UNIX, LINUX, Windows)\n

        \n\u2022 Help Desk management\n</string>

    <string name="careersmainstr">Our philosophy is very simple: clients are best served by consultants who truly focus
        on the employee. That is why we offer a competitive salary and benefits package paired with scheduling
        flexibility to provide an exceptional work-life balance. In addition, we provide unlimited opportunities
        to learn and grow professionally in a creative environment with minimal bureaucracy.
        \n
        \n We continuously endeavor to make sure our employees feel a part of the OPS Consulting Family with OPS Mixers,
        fun events, luncheons, and a Winter Celebration. We interact with our employees on a regular basis and even ask
        for input on how we can strive to make OPS the prime workplace for existing and new employees. If you are looking
        for a company that will provide you with a balanced approach to work and life, OPS is the place for you.
        \n
        \n OPS Consulting is committed to providing equal opportunity to all applicants for employment without regard to race,
        color, religion, sex, age, national origin, disability, veteran status, marital status, sexual orientation, creed,
        or any other applicable protected class status. The majority of our positions require a security clearance and may
        require a background investigation and a polygraph examination. Clearance and polygraph processing will be completed
        by the U.S. Government.</string>

    <string formatted="false" name="careersbenifits"><b>HEALTH INSURANCE</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Individual and Family Plans are available under United Healthcare. Coverage beings on the first day of
        employment.
        \n\u2022 OPS offers two health plans: 1 - Choice HMO with No Deductible and 2 - Choice POS with HSA.
        \n\u2022 OPS funds 80% of ALL plan premiums AND funds 50% of the POS Deductible.
        \n
        \n <b>DENTAL AND VISION INSURANCE</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS offers individual and family plans through Delta Dental PPO Insurance and EyeMed PPO Vision Insurance.
        \n
        \n <b>HEALTH SAVINGS PLAN</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 HSA is a tax-advantaged medical savings account available to employees enrolled in the Choice POS Plan.
        \n
        \n <b>FLEXIBLE SPENDING ACCOUNT &amp; DEPENDENT CARE (FSA and DCAP)</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Take advantage of the FSA and DCAP options to pay medical and dependent care benefits on a pre-tax basis.
        \n
        \n<b>LIFE INSURANCE and AD&amp;D - SHORT &amp; LONG TERM DISABILITY</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides Group Life insurance with a benefit two times your annual salary up to $200,000 at no cost to the
        employee.
        \n\u2022 OPS provides Short Term and Long Term Disability coverage at no cost to the employee.
        \n\u2022 Voluntary life insurance, which includes coverage for spouse and children, is also available to employees.
        \n
        \n<b>401K PACKAGE</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS offers a Safe Harbor 401(k) Plan with immediate and 100% vesting upon enrollment.
        \n\u2022 The Company will match 5%, dollar for dollar, of your 5% contribution
        \n
        \n<b>PAID TIME-OFF</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides its employees with 4 weeks of PTO January 1st of each year.
        \n\u2022 At the end of each year, carry over one week to the following year or cash out unused PTO
        \n
        \n<b>HOURLY COMP TIME</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS matches one hour of PTO for every extra hour worked on contract per week.
        \n
        \n<b>HOLIDAYS</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides 10 paid holidays per year – any of which can be used as floating holidays if contract allows.
        \n
        \n<b>EMERGENCY and ADMIN HOURS</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides Emergency and Admin hours to employees so they may attend a company meeting or stay home during
        inclement weather without having to use PTO or make up time.
        \n
        \n<b>TRAINING &amp; PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides employees $5000 ANNUALLY toward approved education courses, training, and certifications.
        \n\u2022 OPS encourages personal and professional growth by supporting goals set by our employees in their Personal
        Development Plans.
        \n
        \n<b>SPOT AWARDS</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 Exceptional performance and professional development are rewarded throughout an employee\’s career with OPS.
        In addition to annual assessments, OPS provides Spot Awards for key performers!
        \n
        \n<b>WELLNESS SERVICES</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS provides all employees with a membership card offering 20% discounts for all spa and wellness services at
        the Face Place Spa and Wellness Center in Columbia, MD.
        \n
        \n<b>EMPLOYEE REFERRAL BONUS</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS offers employees an unlimited $7500 BONUS for the referral of each qualified candidate who is subsequently
        hired by the Company.
        \n
        \n<b>PAID MILITARY LEAVE</b>
        \n
        \n\u2022 OPS supports our men and women in uniform. Reservists will be granted up to 10 days of absence per year with
        pay for reserve duty while receiving regular pay. OPS also takes measures to support military personnel who receive
        involuntary deployment orders.
</string>

    <string name="jobDescriptions">At OPS Consulting, we offer jobs in Annapolis Junction (MD), College Park (MD), Hanover (MD),
        Bolling AFB (Washington D.C.), McLean (VA), Northern Virginia, Augusta (GA), and San Antonio (TX). General job categories
        include: Junior, Mid-Level, and Senior Intelligence Analysts, Junior, Mid-Level, and Senior Software Engineers, Financial
        Analysts, Acquisition Professionals, and Systems Engineers. Visit our website to look at in-depth descriptions of all our
        available positions.
</string>

</resources>
